Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Horace Walpole's Correspondence, 1725-1797; Series I; 12
  - Conway, Henry Seymour *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1755 Nov 27 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 418-20.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1755 Dec 11 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 421-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Jan 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 425-28.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1756 Jan 22 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 428-31. Toynbee iii, p. 385-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Feb 20 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 440-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Mar 6 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 448-50.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1756 Mar 25 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 451-55. Toynbee iii, p. 407.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Apr 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 455-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Apr 29 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 461-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Jun 29 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 467-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Jul 6 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 470-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Jul 25 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 472-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 475-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Oct 24 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 478.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1756 Oct 28 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 479-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 May 29 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 483-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Jun 9 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 485-86.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Jun 12 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 487.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Jun 16 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 488-89.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Jul 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 490-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Aug 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 493-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Aug 11 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 495-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Aug 29 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 499-501.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Sep 3 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 501-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Sep 7 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 503-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Sep 26 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 506-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 507-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 7 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 512.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 8 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 513-14. Toynbee iv, p. 100.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 10 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 514-16.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Oct 13 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 519-20.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1757 Nov 24 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 520-21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 [Mar 16 or 23?] (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 523-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 May 28 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 526-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Jun 11 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 532-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Jun 16 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 538.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Probably a draft, in Henry Seymour Conway's hand), 1758 Jul 4 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 539-43.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Jul 8 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 543-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Jul 20 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 546-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Jul 27 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 552-53.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Aug 1 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 553-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Aug 11 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 557-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Aug 11 bis (Box 8, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 559.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Aug 27 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 559-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Sep 17 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 564-68.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Sep 19 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 568-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Sep 28 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 573-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Oct 15 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 576-79.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Oct 17 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 579-83.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1758 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 37, p. 583-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Jan 21 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 3-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Jan 28 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 9-11.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 May 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Jun 17 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 13-15.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Aug 14 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 20-24.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Sep 13 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 27-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Oct 11 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 30-33.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Oct 14 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 34-36.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 Jun 21 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 38, p. 55-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Aug 9 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 83-84.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1767 Sep 9 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 87-89.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Jun 16 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 98-103.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Aug 25 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 107-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Jan 22 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 121-22.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Jan 24 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 123-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Mar 20 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 125-26.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1771 Jun 17 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 138-40.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1775 Jan 22 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 245-48.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1775 Aug 9 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 251-53.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jun 3 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 348.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Fragment of cover only), 1782 Feb (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 388. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 Aug 20 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 390-91.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Jun 24 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 448-52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Jul 20 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 453-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1789 May 26 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 464-66.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Jun 25 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 474-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1790 Dec 23 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 480-84.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Cover only), 1792 Aug 7 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 491.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1793 Sep 22 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 501-7.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Cover only), 1794 Jan 10 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 508.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Cover only), 1795 Jul 7 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 39, p. 511.
  - Copleston, Thomas
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Fragment), 1745 Jan 27 OS (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 50-51. Not in Toynbee.
  - Copley, John Singleton *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1793 May 21 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 391. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 308.
  - Corke, 5th Earl of
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1759 Feb 14 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 161. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 159.
  - Cosway, Richard
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1787 Jan 30 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 187. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 47-48.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1789 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 233. Not in Toynbee.
  - Coutts, Thomas
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Dec 7 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 340. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 73.
  - Cowslade, John
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, [1780?] Oct 13 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 419-20. Not in Toynbee.
  - Craon, Prince and Princess de *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 9 NS (Box 9, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 37-39. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 80-81.
  - Craon, Prince de
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 May 1 NS (Box 9, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 53. Not in Toynbee.
  - Craven, Elizabeth, Baroness
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Feb 17 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 336-38. Toynbee Supp. ii, p. 148-50.
  - Dacre, 17th Baron
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 Jun 9 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 197-200. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 2-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Apr 30 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 185-86. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 219.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1778 Dec 15 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 392. Not in Toynbee.
  - Dalrymple, Sir David (Lord Hailes) *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Jun 29 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 26-27. Toynbee iv, p. 151-52.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Jul 11 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 31-35. Toynbee iv, p. 278-80.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Sep 5 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 36-37. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Dec 7 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 38. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Feb 25 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 46-48. Toynbee iv, p. 243-45.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Mar 25 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 52-55. Toynbee iv, p. 252-54.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 May 22 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 55-57. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Jun 19 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 57-58. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1759 Oct 15 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 58-61. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 Feb 3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 61-64. Toynbee iv, p. 349-51.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 Apr 4 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 64-67. Toynbee iv, p. 367-70.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 May 15 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 67-68. Toynbee iv, p. 388-89.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1760 Jun 28 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 69-71. Toynbee iv, p. 398-400.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 Apr 14 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 71-72. Toynbee v, p. 50-51.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 Nov 30 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 73-76. Toynbee v, p. 148-49.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1761 Dec 21 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 76-78. Toynbee v, p. 153-54.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 Jan 18 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 82-84. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 Feb 13 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 84-85. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 85-87. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1763 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 88-90. Toynbee v, 318-20.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1763 Jul 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 90-91. Toynbee v, 347.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Jan 31 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 91-93. Toynbee v, 448-49.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 9 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 13 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 23 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 94-99. Toynbee vi, 17-20.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Apr 9 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 100-101. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1764 Sep (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 101-2. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1766 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 107-8. Toynbee vi, p. 456-57.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1767 Nov 8 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 110-15. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Jan 17 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 115-17. Toynbee vii, p. 157-59.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Feb 2 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 118-19. Toynbee vii, p. 160.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1768 Oct 26 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 122-24. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1769 Aug 15 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 126-27. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1769 Dec 14 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 127. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1770 Jan 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 127-29. Toynbee vii, p. 347-48.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1770 Jan 23 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 129-31. Toynbee vii, p. 359-61.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1773 Dec 14 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 134-35. Toynbee viii, p. 379.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1779 Mar 12 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 140-41. Toynbee x, p. 390.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1780 Dec 11 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 141-46. Toynbee xi, p. 333-36.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1781 Jan 1 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 146-50. Toynbee xi, p. 351-54.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1781 Feb 10 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 151-56. Toynbee xi, p. 392-95.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1790 Sep 21 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 204-8. Toynbee xiv, p. 291-93.
    - To (?) Dalrymple, letter from Horace Walpole, 1792 Jul 3 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 15, p. 214. Not in Toynbee.
  - Delany, Mrs Mary
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1774 after Apr 7 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 275-76. Not in Toynbee.
  - Drumgold, John
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 15 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 302. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 179-82.
  - Ducarel, Andrew Coltee *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 Jan 12 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 120-21. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1758 May 21 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 128. Toynbee iv, p. 142.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Draft in Andrew Coltee Ducarel's hand), 1762 Feb 23 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 212.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 Feb 24 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 218-19. Toynbee v, p. 178-79.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Draft in Andrew Coltee Ducarel's hand), 1762 Feb 27 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 220.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Draft in Andrew Coltee Ducarel's hand), 1762 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 247-48. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1767 Apr 25 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 80. Toynbee vii, p. 104.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Draft in Andrew Coltee Ducarel's hand), 1768 Feb 6 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      See note in Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 123.
  - Du Deffand, Madame *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (in the hand of Madame de Jonzac), 1766 May (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 3, p. 51.
      Using the name Madame de Sévigné.
      With auction receipt.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Copy in Horace Walpole's hand), 1766 May (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Extract of a letter from Horace Walpole (in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1766 Jul 16 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 3, p. 94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Apr 10 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 5, p. 57-63.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in an unknown hand; postscript in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1774 Dec 26 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 6, p. 124-25.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (Fragment), 1775 Apr 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 6, p. 175.
  - Duncannon, Viscount
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1786 Nov 29 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 180-81. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 46-47.
  - Edgcumbe, 1st Baron
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Sep 26 OS (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 53-54. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 123-24.
  - Edgcumbe, 2d Baron
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Aug 10 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 65-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Sep 10 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 78-79.
  - Egremont, 2d Earl of
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Apr 21 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 281-82. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 177.
  - Elderton, Rev. John
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1796 Aug 4 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 442-43. Not in Toynbee.
  - Elie de Beaumont, Mme
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Apr 26 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 173-74.
  - Elie de Beaumont, Jean-Baptiste-Jacques
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Draft in Horace Walpole's hand), 1765 Mar 18 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 378-80. Toynbee vi, p. 200-202.
  - Ellis, Welbore
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, [1788 Aug 23?] (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 224-25. Not in Toynbee.
  - [Essex, James?]
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1772 Nov 13 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 235. Not in Toynbee.
  - Fenn, John *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1774 Sep 17 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 232-35.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Enclosure only), Circa 1777 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 235.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1781 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 236-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Jan 2 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 238-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 May 4 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 240-42.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1782 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 243-44.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1789 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 246.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1789 May 16 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1789 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 246-47.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1789 Jun 1 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 247.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1791 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 247-48.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Cover only), 1793 Jul 2 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 248.
  - Fenn, Mrs John
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1784 Jul 7 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 16, p. 244-45.
  - Forcalquier, Comtesse de
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (French translation in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1766 Sep 8 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 33-35. Toynbee vii, p. 43-45.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (French translation in Jean-François Wiart's hand), 1766 Oct 27 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 40-42. Toynbee vii, p. 58-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 early Aug (Box 11, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 93-94. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 mid-Aug (Box 11, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 161-63. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 209-11.
  - Fox, Charles James
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Aug 6 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 41, p. 27. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 204.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Sep 10 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 73-74. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 288-89.
  - Fox, Henry *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1746 Jul 19 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 99-101.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jul 22 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 102-3.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1746 Jul 24 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 104-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Oct 9 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 107-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1747 Oct 30 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 110-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1748 Mar 28 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 112-13.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1748 Oct 20 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 116-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1752 Nov 23 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 119.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1754 Mar 13 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 122-23.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1756 Dec 20 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 131.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jun 11 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 189-91.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (in an unknown hand; signature and some corrections in Henry Fox's hand), 1765 Jun 11 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 229-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Aug 14 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 246-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole (in an unknown hand), 1767 Aug 16 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 30, p. 248-49. Toynbee Supp. i, p. 161.
  - French, Richard
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1790 Feb 14 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 267-72. Toynbee Supp. iii, p. 296-301.
  - Garrick, Mrs David *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1794 Oct 25 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 410. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (in Thomas Kirgate's hand), 1796 Jan 11 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 426-27. Not in Toynbee.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1796 Apr 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 42, p. 434. Not in Toynbee.
  - Gazetteer, Printer of *
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1762 Sep (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 40, p. 256-57. Not in Toynbee.
  - George, Prince of Wales (George IV)